University of Connecticut 1987.0011
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series III: State Government, undated, 1952-1986
  - Legislative inquiries
    - Beck, Audrey, 1975-1978, 1983 (Box 26:, Folder 882-883)
    - Cohen, Morris, 1976 March - June (Box 26:, Folder 884)
    - D, 1983 May - June (Box 26:, Folder 885)
    - Glassman, A., 1975-1979 (Box 26:, Folder 886)
    - Goodwin, Dorothy, 1952-1975 (Box 26:, Folder 887)
    - Hinds, Boyd, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 888)
    - Houley, Robert D., 1975-1978 (Box 26:, Folder 889)
    - Klebanoff, H., 1975-1977 (Box 26:, Folder 890)
    - M, 1975-1980 (Box 26:, Folder 891)
    - R, 1974-1979 (Box 26:, Folder 892)
    - Rome, Lewis B., 1976-1978 (Box 26:, Folder 893)
    - S, 1975-1977 (Box 26:, Folder 894)
    - Stevens, Gerald, 1976-1978 (Box 26:, Folder 895)
    - Stolb, Irving, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 896)
    - Strada, 1976 (Box 26:, Folder 897)
    - W, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 898)
  - Legislative Review and Investigations Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 26:, Folder 899)
  - Lieutenant Governor Killian, 1975-1977, 1983 (Box 26:, Folder 900-901)
  - Mansfield Training School, 1976 (Box 26:, Folder 902)
  - N, 1984 (Box 26:, Folder 903)
  - Naugatuck Valley Regional Higher Education Center, 1974-1983 (Box 26:, Folder 904-906)
  - North Central Region Coordinating Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 26:, Folder 907-908)
  - O, 1984 (Box 26:, Folder 909)
  - Office of Inter-Governmental Programs, 1977 (Box 26:, Folder 910)
  - Office of Legislative Research, 1976-1982 (Box 26:, Folder 911)
  - Office of management and Budget, 1978 (Box 26:, Folder 912)
  - Office of Policy and Management, 1977-1983 (Box 26:, Folder 913-915)
  - P, 1984 (Box 27:, Folder 916)
  - Power of facility: evaluation control, 1978-1980 (Box 27:, Folder 917)
  - Power Utilities Control Authority, 1976 (Box 27:, Folder 918)
  - Public Works Department, 1974-1978 (Box 27:, Folder 919)
  - Restructuring of Public Higher Education, 1976-1977 (Box 27:, Folder 920-921)
  - Secretary of State, 1976-1978, 1980 (Box 27:, Folder 922-923)
  - State Library, 1978 (Box 27:, Folder 924)
  - State Personnel Division, 1975-1983 (Box 27:, Folder 925)
  - State Retirement Commission, 1976-1977 (Box 27:, Folder 926)
  - State Treasurer, 1974-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 27:, Folder 927-928)
  - T, 1984 Nov (Box 27:, Folder 929)
  - Veterans Administration, 1977-1981 (Box 27:, Folder 930)
  - Voting records, 1982 February - March (Box 27:, Folder 931)
  - W, 1984 May (Box 27:, Folder 932)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1977-1979 (Box 27:, Folder 933)
- Series IV: Federal Government, undated, 1973-1986
  - Action, 1977-1979 (Box 27:, Folder 934)
  - Air Force, 1978-1983 (Box 27:, Folder 935-936)
  - Bankhead-Jones Act, 1976-1982 (Box 27:, Folder 937)
  - Buckley Amendment, 1974-1976 (Box 27:, Folder 938)
  - Budget cuts, 1980-1982 (Box 27:, Folder 939-941)
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1982 January - March (Box 27:, Folder 942)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1974 (Box 27:, Folder 943)
  - College tuition, Tax Relief Act (S.311), 1977 (Box 27:, Folder 944)
  - Congress and Senate
    - Denardis, Lawrence J., 1980-1982 (Box 27:, Folder 945)
    - Kennelly, Barbara, 1980-1983 (Box 27:, Folder 946)
  - Congressional Delegation: telegrams/letters, 1980 April - May (Box 27:, Folder 947)
  - Congressional inquiries, 1980-1983 (Box 27:, Folder 948)
    - William Cotter, 1976-1981 (Box 27:, Folder 949)
  - Congressional and senatorial inquiries, 1984 March - October (Box 27:, Folder 950)
    - Dodd, Christopher, 1976-1983 (Box 27:, Folder 951-952)
    - Giaimo, Robert N., 1976-1981 (Box 27:, Folder 953)
    - M - Z, 1976-1984 (Box 28:, Folder 954-955)
  - Congress
    - Dodd, Christopher - John A. DiBiaggio Washington visit), 1979 (Box 28:, Folder 956)
    - McKinney, Stewart B., 1976-1982 (Box 28:, Folder 957-958)
    - Moffet, Toby A., 1976-1982 (Box 28:, Folder 959-960)
  - Copyright Revision Act of 1976 Department of, 1977-1978 (Box 28:, Folder 961)
    - Agriculture, 1976-1977, 1984 (Box 28:, Folder 962-963)
    - Commerce, 1981-1982 (Box 28:, Folder 964-965)
    - Education, 1981 (Box 28:, Folder 966)
    - Education Coalition, 1981 (Box 28:, Folder 967)
    - Health, Education and Welfare, 1974-1980 (Box 28:, Folder 968-973)
    - Health and Human Services, 1980 July, 1981-1984 (Box 28:, Folder 974-976)
    - Labor: Federal Contract Compliance Program, 1976-1983 (Box 28:, Folder 977-979)
    - State, 1974-1978 (Box 28:, Folder 980)
  - Dodd Washington Seminar, 1983 October 26 - 28 (Box 28:, Folder 981)
  - E, 1979-1981 (Box 28:, Folder 982)
  - Education Appropriations Bill (HR 5901), 1975 (Box 28:, Folder 983)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 28:, Folder 984)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 985)
  - F, 1977 (Box 28:, Folder 986)
  - Federal budget, 1977-1978, 1980, 1983 (Box 28:, Folder 987-989)
  - Federal Legislation, undated (Box 28:, Folder 990)
  - Federal Legislative Issues: higher education, 1975-1979, 1983 (Box 28:, Folder 991-993)
  - Foundation for International Technological Cooperation, 1978 (Box 28:, Folder 994)
  - Handicap: Section 504, 1983-1986 (Box 28:, Folder 996-997)
  - Higher and continuing education, 1979 (Box 28:, Folder 998)
  - Higher Education, Action Committee for, 1985 (Box 28:, Folder 999)
  - Higher Education Re-Authorization (H.R.5192), 1979-1980 (Box 28:, Folder 1000)
  - Internship Program, federal, 1976-1983 (Box 28:, Folder 1001-1003)
  - L, 1979 (Box 28:, Folder 1004)
  - Miscellaneous
    - A - Z, 1981-1983 (Box 28:, Folder 1005)
    - D, 1984 January - May (Box 28:, Folder 1006)
    - F, 1984 August - September (Box 28:, Folder 1007)
    - N, 1976-1980 (Box 28:, Folder 1008)
  - National Advisory Council on Health Professions Education, 1979-1980 (Box 28:, Folder 1009)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1978-1981 (Box 28:, Folder 1010)
  - National Institute of Health, 1982-1983 (Box 28:, Folder 1011)
  - National Medal of Science, 1978-1979 (Box 28:, Folder 1012-1013)
  - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 1983 June - September (Box 28:, Folder 1014)
  - National Science Foundation, 1975-1981 (Box 28:, Folder 1015-1016)
  - Naval Submarine Base, Groton, 1979 (Box 28:, Folder 1017)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1974-1976, 1984 (Box 28:, Folder 1018-1019)
  - Office of Civil Rights, 1981 March - July (Box 28:, Folder 1020)
  - Office of Surface Mining, 1978-1979 (Box 28:, Folder 1021)
  - Small Business Innovation Research Act, 1989-1981 (Box 29:, Folder 1022)
  - Student financial aid, 1979-1984 (Box 29:, Folder 1023-1025)
  - T, 1977 (Box 29:, Folder 1026)
  - Testimony: Washington, 1983 April - March (Box 29:, Folder 1027)
  - Title I, 1979 (Box 29:, Folder 1028)
  - Title III, 1974-1979 (Box 29:, Folder 1029)
  - Title III/XII, 1984 (Box 29:, Folder 1030)
  - Title VI, 1973-1976 (Box 29:, Folder 1031-1032)
  - Title XII, 1977-1983 (Box 29:, Folder 1033-1034)
  - Title XX, 1975-1981 (Box 29:, Folder 1035-1036)
  - U.S. Military Academy, 1978-1979 (Box 29:, Folder 1037-1039)
  - U.S. Postal Service, 1974-1984 (Box 29:, Folder 1040-1041)
  - U.S. Savings bonds, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 29:, Folder 1042)
  - Veterans Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 29:, Folder 1043)
  - Washington meeting, 1980 August - September (Box 29:, Folder 1044)
  - White House Fellowship, 1977-1978 (Box 29:, Folder 1045)
- Series V: Educational Associations, 1973-1984
  - A, 1977-1984 (Box 30:, Folder 1046-1048)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Slavic Studies, 1975-1978 (Box 30:, Folder 1049)
  - American Association of State colleges and Universities, 1974-1983 (Box 30:, Folder 1050)
  - American Association of University Women, 1976-1980 (Box 30:, Folder 1051-1052)
  - American Council on Education, 1974-1982 (Box 30:, Folder 1053-1058)
    - Annual meeting, 1983 September - October (Box 30:, Folder 1059)
    - Fellows, Rose Quezeda, 1981-1983 (Box 30:, Folder 1060)
    - Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 30:, Folder 1061)
    - Seminar reports, 1975 (Box 30:, Folder 1062)
  - American Physical Therapy Association, 1976-1978 (Box 30:, Folder 1063)
  - American Universities Field Staff, Inc., 1964-1978 (Box 30:, Folder 1064-1065)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1974-1980 (Box 30:, Folder 1066)
    - Newsletters, 1974-1976 (Box 30:, Folder 1067)
  - Association of College Honor Societies, 1976-1978 (Box 30:, Folder 1068)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1975-1978 (Box 30:, Folder 1069)
  - C, 1982, 1984 (Box 30:, Folder 1070)
  - College Entrance Exam Board, 1975-1983 (Box 30:, Folder 1071)
  - College and University Business Instructors of CT, 1975-1976 (Box 30:, Folder 1072)
  - Committee on Government: University Relationships in support of Science, 1982 (Box 30:, Folder 1073)
  - Connecticut Academy of Science and Engineering, 1979-1981 (Box 30:, Folder 1074)
  - Cooperative Assessment of Experimental Learning, 1974-1975 (Box 30:, Folder 1075)
  - Council for Advancement and Support of Education, 1976-1982 (Box 30:, Folder 1076-1077)
  - Council for International Exchange of Scholars, 1975-1977 (Box 30:, Folder 1078)
  - Educational Testing Services, 1975-1976 (Box 30:, Folder 1079)
  - EDUCOM, 1974-1976 (Box 30:, Folder 1080)
  - International Association of University Presidents, 1976-1978 (Box 30:, Folder 1081)
  - International Research and Exchange Board, 1976-1979 (Box 30:, Folder 1082)
  - National Association of Extension Home Economists, 1982 (Box 30:, Folder 1083)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1977-1979 (Box 30:, Folder 1084-1085)
    - Annual meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 31:, Folder 1092)
    - Conventions, 1974-1979 (Box 31:, Folder 1093)
    - Executive Committee>, 1983 (Box 31:, Folder 1094)
    - Files, 1985 (Box 31:, Folder 1095)
    - For Your Information, 1975-1978 (Box 31:, Folder 1096)
    - International Affairs Committee, 1983 (Box 31:, Folder 1097)
    - Legal Affairs Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 31:, Folder 1098)
    - Legal Affairs Feasibility Study, 1977-1978 (Box 31:, Folder 1099)
    - Legislative Network, 1981-1982 (Box 31:, Folder 1100)
    - President's Seminar, 1980 September - October (Box 31:, Folder 1101)
    - Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 31:, Folder 1102)
    - University Presidents, 1975 November (Box 31:, Folder 1103)
  - National Center for Higher Education Management System, 1983 (Box 31:, Folder 1104)
  - National Commission for Cooperative Education, 1978 June - September (Box 31:, Folder 1105)
  - National University Extension Association, 1974 (Box 31:, Folder 1106)
  - New England Association of Schools and Colleges, 1973-1984 (Box 31:, Folder 1107-1112)
  - New England Board of Higher Education, 1974-1984 (Box 32:, Folder 1113-1127)
  - New England Center for Continuing Education, 1973-1979 (Box 33:, Folder 1128)
  - New England Land Grant Universities
    - Council of Presidents, 1980-1984 (Box 33:, Folder 1129-1138)
    - Council of Presidents, Joint Operations Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 33:, Folder 1139-1135)
    - Council of Presidents, Joint Operations Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 34:, Folder 1136-1137)
  - New England Center for Continuing Education, 1973-1979 (Box 34:, Folder 1138-1141)
  - New England Council, Inc., 1978-1982 (Box 34:, Folder 1142)
  - New England Regional Computing Program, 1975-1977 (Box 34:, Folder 1143)
  - Organization for Tropical Studies, Inc., 1975-1983 (Box 34:, Folder 1144-1145)
  - Universities Council on Water Resources, Inc., 1983 (Box 34:, Folder 1146)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1973 (Box 34:, Folder 1147)
- Series VI: Subject Files, 1974-1986
  - A, 1977-1986 (Box 34:, Folder 1148-1150)
  - Advisory Committee on the Handicapped Sec 504, 1977-1983 (Box 34:, Folder 1151)
  - Aetna Institute for Corporate Education, 1982-1983 (Box 34:, Folder 1152)
  - Aetna Life & Casualty Aid to Education Program, 1976-1977 (Box 34:, Folder 1153)
  - American Enterprise Institute, 1979 (Box 34:, Folder 1154)
  - Annhurst College, 1980 February - March (Box 34:, Folder 1155)
  - Architects, 1978 August 17 - 28 (Box 34:, Folder 1156)
  - Area Health Education Council, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 1157)
  - Assistant to President for Government Relations, 1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1158)
  - Atlanta crisis, 1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1159)
  - B, 1974-1980 (Box 34:, Folder 1160-1161)
  - Babbidge, Homer, 1975-1977 (Box 34:, Folder 1162)
  - Bakke case, 1977-1978 (Box 34:, Folder 1163)
  - Barnes, Bartlett, 1981-1982 (Box 34:, Folder 1164)
  - Barron's Profiles, 1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1165)
  - B'nai Brith, 1979-1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1166)
  - Bolger, Raymond W., 1976-1977 (Box 34:, Folder 1167)
  - Boy Scouts, 1979 (Box 34:, Folder 1168)
  - Brand-Rex Company, 1979-1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1169-1170)
  - C, 1974-1982 (Box 34:, Folder 1171-1173)
  - Career counseling, 1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1174)
  - Carnegie Council, 1974-1978 (Box 34:, Folder 1175)
  - CASE, 1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1176)
  - Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 34:, Folder 1177-1178)
  - Charles E. Merrill Trust, 1974-1975 (Box 34:, Folder 1179)
  - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1975-1979 (Box 34:, Folder 1180)
  - Choate Rosemary Hall, 1977 September - October (Box 34:, Folder 1181)
  - The Citadel, 1976-1982 (Box 34:, Folder 1182-1183)
  - City of Hartford, 1976-1979 (Box 34:, Folder 1184)
  - Colonial Bancorp, 1979-1980 (Box 34:, Folder 1185)
  - Combined Health Appeal, 1977-1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1186-1188)
  - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities Connecticut, 1979-1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1189)
  - Connecticut
    - Broadcasters Association, 1975 May 8 - 16 (Box 34:, Folder 1190)
    - Business and Industry Association, 1975-1978 (Box 34:, Folder 1191)
    - Conference of Independent Colleges, 1980-1983 (Box 34:, Folder 1192)
    - Conference of Municipalities, 1979-1980 (Box 34:, Folder 1193)
    - Faculty Talent Search Program (CONNFACTS), 1974-1975 (Box 34:, Folder 1194)
    - Humanities Council, 1976-1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1195)
    - Jaycees, 1980-1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1196)
    - Public Expenditure Council, Inc., 1981-1982; (2 folders) (Box 34:, Folder 1197)
    - Public Television, 1977-1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1198)
    - State Labor Council, 1979-1980 (Box 34:, Folder 1199)
  - Continental Oil Company, 1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1200)
  - Costa Rica, 1976-1977 (Box 34:, Folder 1201)
  - Council for Moral Leadership, 1974-1976 (Box 34:, Folder 1202)
  - C.V. Mosby Company, 1979-1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1203)
  - D, 1979 (Box 34:, Folder 1204)
  - Dansforth Foundation, 1976-1980 (Box 34:, Folder 1205-1206)
  - DOW Chemical U.S.A., 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 1207)
  - Eastern Connecticut State College, 1979 (Box 34:, Folder 1208)
  - Ella Grasso Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box 34:, Folder 1209)
  - Emergency Operations Plan, 1980 (Box 34:, Folder 1210)
  - Financial Executives Institute of Southern Connecticut, 1980-1981 (Box 34:, Folder 1211)
  - Franklin Library, 1976-1978 (Box 34:, Folder 1212)
  - Flanagan, Dennis: consultant, 1982 Jul-Nov (Box 34:, Folder 1213)
  - Ford Foundation, 1977-1980 (Box 35:, Folder 1214-1215)
  - Furlan, Nicola, 1979-1981 (Box 35:, Folder 1216)
  - Furniture stored at Southeastern, 1979-1981 (Box 35:, Folder 1217)
  - General Electric Foundation, 1975-1983 (Box 35:, Folder 1218-1219)
  - Greater Hartford Business Development Center, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 1220)
  - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce, 1979-1982 (Box 35:, Folder 1221)
    - Ambassador Club, 1976-1978 (Box 35:, Folder 1222)
    - Congress Club, 1978 March - April (Box 35:, Folder 1223)
  - Greater Hartford Convention and Visitors Bureau, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 35:, Folder 1224)
  - Greater Willimantic Chamber of Commerce, 1978-1979 (Box 35:, Folder 1225)
  - Green, Daniel B., 1979 Aug-Nov (Box 35:, Folder 1226)
  - Gurleyville Grist Mill, 1979-1980 (Box 35:, Folder 1227)
  - H, 1979-1982 (Box 35:, Folder 1228)
  - Hackman, Florence, 1978-1979 (Box 35:, Folder 1229)
  - Hamilton Standard, 1978 (Box 35:, Folder 1230)
  - Hartford Club, 1977-1982 (Box 35:, Folder 1231)
  - Hartford College for Women, 1976-1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1232)
  - Hartford Courant, 1976-1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1233)
  - Hartford Hospital, 1979-1981 (Box 35:, Folder 1234)
  - Hartford Steam Boiler, 1979 September - November (Box 35:, Folder 1235)
  - Hubert H. Humphrey Fellowship Program, 1979 December 14 - 2 (Box 35:, Folder 1236)
  - Inquiries, A - Z, 1978-1979 (Box 35:, Folder 1237)
  - Insurance Association of Connecticut, 1975 October - December (Box 35:, Folder 1238)
  - Ivry, David A., 1976 (Box 35:, Folder 1239)
  - Job Offers, 1978 March - September (Box 35:, Folder 1240)
  - Keeney, Mary, 1981 (Box 35:, Folder 1241)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1979 March - December (Box 35:, Folder 1242)
  - Kent State University, 1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1243)
  - Ketchum, Inc., 1976-1978 (Box 35:, Folder 1244)
  - Konowitch, Bonnie, 1976-1978 (Box 35:, Folder 1245)
  - Krupp, Judith, 1979 (Box 35:, Folder 1246)
  - M, 1980-1981 (Box 35:, Folder 1247)
  - Manufacturers Association of Hartford County, 1978 (Box 35:, Folder 1248)
  - March of Dimes, 1979-1980 (Box 35:, Folder 1249)
  - Merrill Trust [See: Charles E. Merrill Trust]
  - Moreland, Wallace S., 1976 April - May (Box 35:, Folder 1250)
  - Music use, licensing information, 1980 (Box 35:, Folder 1251)
  - N, 1976-1985 (Box 35:, Folder 1252-1253)
  - National Alliance of Business, 1979 (Box 35:, Folder 1254)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1982-1983 (Box 35:, Folder 1255)
  - National Jewish Hospital/National Asthma Center, 1981-1982 (Box 35:, Folder 1256)
  - National Council on Philanthropy, 1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1257)
  - New England Public Policy Institute, 1977 June - November (Box 35:, Folder 1258)
  - New London Day, 1975-1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1259)
  - New York Times, 1977, 1982-1983 (Box 35:, Folder 1260-1261)
  - Noble, Daniel E., 1977 Jan-Feb (Box 35:, Folder 1262)
  - Northeast Regional Studies Association, 1975-1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1263)
  - Nuclear Arms Freeze Week, 1982-1983 (Box 35:, Folder 1264)
  - O, 1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1265)
  - P, 1976-1981 (Box 35:, Folder 1266)
  - Partners of the Americans, 1976 January - August (Box 35:, Folder 1267)
  - Perkin-Elmer Corporation, 1978-1982 (Box 35:, Folder 1268-1269)
  - Pfizer, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 35:, Folder 1270)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1975 (Box 35:, Folder 1271)
  - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft Group, 1978 February - March (Box 35:, Folder 1272)
  - President, 1979 (Box 35:, Folder 1273)
  - President's reports, 1975-1977 (Box 35:, Folder 1274)
  - Publications, 1979-1981 (Box 35:, Folder 1275)
  - Publications submitted but rejected, 1981 October - November (Box 35:, Folder 1276)
  - Questionnaires, 1976-1977 (Box 36:, Folder 1277)
  - Questionnaires completed, 1982-1983 (Box 36:, Folder 1278)
  - R, 1974-1984 (Box 36:, Folder 1279-1281)
  - Ramsey, Nancy, 1979 (Box 36:, Folder 1282)
  - Reilly, Owen, 1974-1975 (Box 36:, Folder 1283)
  - Reisner, Allan K., 1975-1976 (Box 36:, Folder 1284)
  - Republic of China, 1978 December 20 - 26 (Box 36:, Folder 1285)
  - Research Corporation, 1976-1979 (Box 36:, Folder 1286)
  - Rogers Corporation, 1980 January - March, 1982 April - May (Box 36:, Folder 1287-1288)
  - Rutgers State University of New Jersey, 1975-1976 (Box 36:, Folder 1289)
  - S, 1976-1981 (Box 36:, Folder 1290)
  - Sacred Heart University, 1977-1982 (Box 36:, Folder 1291-1292)
  - Salary, 1979-1980 (Box 36:, Folder 1293)
  - Sandquist, Muriel, 1975-1978 (Box 36:, Folder 1294)
  - Sloan Foundation, 1974-1976, 1980 Oct-Nov (Box 36:, Folder 1295-1296)
  - Sohlberg, Leonard E., 1974-1975 (Box 36:, Folder 1297)
  - South African Education Program, 1980-1982 (Box 36:, Folder 1298)
  - T, 1977-1981 (Box 36:, Folder 1299)
  - Texas Instruments Foundation, 1977-1978 (Box 36:, Folder 1300)
  - Texas Instruments Founders Prize, 1979-1980 (Box 36:, Folder 1301)
  - Torrington Area Foundation for Public Giving, 1975-1981 (Box 36:, Folder 1302)
  - Town of Windham, 1979 (Box 36:, Folder 1303)
  - Travelers Insurance Companies, 1977-1983 (Box 36:, Folder 1304)
  - Trecker, Harleigh B., 1978-1979 (Box 36:, Folder 1305)
  - Trinity College, 1975-1977 (Box 36:, Folder 1306)
  - U, 1978-1980 (Box 36:, Folder 1307)
  - United Nations University, 1973-1974 (Box 36:, Folder 1308)
  - United States Military Academy, 1980-1981 (Box 36:, Folder 1309)
  - United Technologies, 1978-1981 (Box 36:, Folder 1310)
  - United Technologies Corporation, 1982 November 5 - 29 (Box 36:, Folder 1311)
  - United Technologies Research Center, 1974-1978 (Box 36:, Folder 1312)
  - United Way, 1977-1983 (Box 36:, Folder 1313-1314)
  - University of Bridgeport, 1982 April - June (Box 36:, Folder 1315)
  - University of Hartford, 1975-1983 (Box 36:, Folder 1316)
  - University of Pennsylvania Board of Overseers, 1979-1981 (Box 36:, Folder 1317)
  - University of Vermont, 1975 (Box 36:, Folder 1318)
  - V, 1979-1981 (Box 36:, Folder 1319)
  - Virginia credit, 1980 (Box 36:, Folder 1320)
  - W, 1970-1982 (Box 36:, Folder 1321-1322)
  - Welsh, Thomas J., 1976-1977 (Box 36:, Folder 1323)
  - WFSB-TV 3, 1976-1984 (Box 36:, Folder 1324-1325)
  - Willimantic Chronicle, 1976-1977 (Box 36:, Folder 1326)
  - Wilson, Kenneth G., 1982 (Box 36:, Folder 1327)
  - Windham Regional Planning Agency, 1976-1979 (Box 36:, Folder 1328-1329)
  - Wolff, Thomas J., 1983-1984 (Box 36:, Folder 1330)
- Series VII: Speeches, undated, 1977-1985
  - "For UConn-Stamford, Now is the Time to Grow", 1985 January 10 (Box 37:, Folder 1331)
  - "Black History Month", 1985 January 11 (Box 37:, Folder 1332)
  - "Small Business Development Center", 1985 January 25 (Box 37:, Folder 1333)
  - "Statement before the Joint Committee on Appropriations", 1985 February 13 (Box 37:, Folder 1334)
  - "Remarks at Harris Corporation gift dedication, School of Engineering", 1985 March 13 (Box 37:, Folder 1335)
  - "Statement of JAD at the Subcommittee on Education, Arts & Humanities re higher education student financial aid", 1985 March 29 (Box 37:, Folder 1336)
  - "Fifteenth annual Puerto Rican History Month", 1985 March 29 (Box 37:, Folder 1337)
  - "Remarks at meeting of the UConn Senate", 1985 April 8 (Box 37:, Folder 1338)
  - "Remarks before the CT General Assembly re Senate Bill #979", 1985 April 9 (Box 37:, Folder 1339)
  - "Welcoming remarks, Venture Capital Super Symposium", 1985 April 9 (Box 37:, Folder 1340)
  - "Remarks at Spring Initiation ceremony, Phi Kappa Phi", 1985 April 9 (Box 37:, Folder 1341)
  - "Remarks at Honors seminar", 1985 April 10 (Box 37:, Folder 1342)
  - "Commencement address at Eastern Michigan University", 1985 April 20 (Box 37:, Folder 1343)
  - "JAD testimony before the Finance, Revenue, and bonding Committee re enabling legislation for UCEPI land lease", 1985 May 3 (Box 37:, Folder 1344)
  - "Message to the Graduate Resident Magazine", 1985 May 3 (Box 37:, Folder 1345)
  - "Commencement, 1985", 1985 May 19 (Box 37:, Folder 1346)
  - "Commencement address at University of Detroit", 1985 May 26 (Box 37:, Folder 1347)
  - "Members of Class of 1935", 1985 June 1 (Box 37:, Folder 1348)
  - "University of Oklahoma, Honors Convocation", 1985 June 1 (Box 37:, Folder 1349)
  - "Commencement address at University of Oklahoma", 1985 June 2 (Box 37:, Folder 1350)
  - "Special Olympics welcome", 1985 June 14 (Box 37:, Folder 1351)
  - "Statement before Joint Commission on Appropriations of Connecticut General Assembly, 1984 February 15 (Box 37:, Folder 1352)
  - "Homer Daniels Babbidge, Jr.", 1984 February 28 (Box 37:, Folder 1353)
  - "Convocations, remarks by JAD", 1984 February 28 (Box 37:, Folder 1354)
  - "Puerto Rican-Hispanic history observance", 1984 March 20 (Box 37:, Folder 1355)
  - "Spring bloodmobile", 1984 March 20 (Box 37:, Folder 1356)